兹维列夫 7-6³ 6-3 勒纳·钱 · 赛后场上采访
Sasha, you're 5 -1 in matches
萨沙 你的战绩是5胜1负
when the Laver Cup is on the line.
拉沃尔杯胜负悬于一线时
What makes you so clutch
你为什么这么能扛
in the biggest moments in this event?
在这项赛事最关键的时刻？
I don't know. I mean,
我不知道 我是说
I haven't won a match in two years here,
我两年没在这儿赢过一场了
so that's...
所以
I'm happy.
我很开心
I'm happy that I did it today.
我很开心今天做到了
But, you know, I think massive credit
但我觉得要好好称赞
to the entire Team World.
整个世界队
They pushed us all the way again,
他们又一次把我们逼到了最后
and they were champions last year,
他们去年还是冠军
this year.
今年
I think we had a great team.
我觉得我们队伍很棒
We had a great team chemistry, team effort,
化学反应很好 大家齐心协力
and we're definitely happy that we won.
我们当然很高兴赢下来
How big was it for you?
这场对你来说有多重要？
Was it that your team won the doubles prior
是不是因为你们先拿下了双打
to you going out here?
在你上场之前
Did that help your confidence
这有没有给你信心
and free you up a little bit before this match?
让你上场前放松一点？
Yeah, for sure. We have three chances
是的 当然 单打我们有三次机会
to close it out in the singles,
来锁定胜局
and especially with Carlos playing after me,
尤其卡洛斯排在我后面出场
I think that gives me a lot of confidence,
我觉得这给了我很大的信心
gives me a little bit of freedom to play.
也给了我一些自由发挥的空间
But still, it was an incredibly tough match.
但这场比赛还是非常艰难
Credit to Learner as well.
也要称赞勒纳 钱
But I think Carlos is also very happy
不过我想卡洛斯也很高兴
that I closed it out.
是我把比赛拿下了
And me too, by the way.
顺便说一句 我也很高兴
I'm very happy that I won.
我很高兴我赢了
And finally,
最后
you've played this event seven times,
你已经7次参加这项赛事
more than any other player in history.
比历史上任何球员都多
What's your favourite part
你最喜欢哪一部分
of this amazing event here
这项精彩的赛事
at the Laver Cup?
在拉沃尔杯这里？
Winning as a team.
作为一个团队赢球
I think there's no better feeling in sports,
体育里没有比这更好的感觉
winning as a team.
作为一个团队赢球
We don't have enough of it in tennis.
网球里这样的时刻太少了
Being among these great players
能和这些伟大的球员在一起
who I normally see across
平时我每周
the net every single week
都在球网对面见到他们
and playing alongside of them,
现在和他们并肩作战
playing alongside two great captains
跟着两位了不起的队长
with Yannick and Tim.
诺阿和亨曼
Well, one is very good.
嗯 其中一位非常出色
Yannick is the best captain ever,
诺阿是史上最好的队长
and Tim has to work on it a little bit.
亨曼还得再加把劲
I think it's just fun being out here.
我觉得在这里打球就是开心
Awesome. Well, congratulations.
太棒了 恭喜你
Go celebrate with your team.
去和队友们庆祝吧